xnspy.com 2019-06-10

# XNSPY Privacy Policy – How and what information is collected

This Privacy Policy governs the manner, in which XNSPY collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from the users (hereinafter referred to as “User” or “Users”) of the http://www.XNSPY.com Website (hereinafter referred to as “Site”). This Privacy Policy applies to the Site and all the products and services offered by XNSPY. 

### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

We gather two types of information: (1) personally identifiable information that you supply voluntarily when you register for interactive services, order other products or services, or enter certain other areas of our Web sites as noted below in this Privacy Policy and (2) aggregate tracking and site usage information that we gather automatically as you access our Site. 

### Personally Identifiable Information 

We may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit the Site, register, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, and social security number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personally identifiable information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site-related activities. 

Anyone can access our Site, but there are certain areas and services that require registration or provision of certain personal information if accessed, such as by way of example: entering premium content areas, placing advertisements online and making other online purchases, signing up for e-mail newsletters, promotions, contests, sweepstakes or special offers, or participating in reader forums, message boards, chats and reader surveys. If you choose to make a purchase or use such areas, we will ask for certain personally identifiable information, which may include name, mailing address, valid e-mail address and other personal information. Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us at registration, we may send you a welcoming e-mail to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, regarding any information or services you request, and to manage your "account". We will communicate with you by e-mail or other method as directed by you. If you decline to supply or maintain with us certain information while using our Web sites, please understand that you may not be able to use or participate in some or all of the features offered through the Site. 

It is our policy to use the personally identifiable information we acquire at our Site for internal business uses only and to provide content, products and services to you that you value and request. We do not authorize the use of your personal information by any third party (other than XNSPY business services providers discussed in the next section, or, under exceptional conditions as described under "Legal Matters" below). We operate and maintain a variety of online security measures to safeguard and keep your information private. 

### Links to Other Sites 

Our Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that is linked to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by the Sites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may change occasionally. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Your browsing through and interacting with any other Site, including Sites, which are linked to our Site, is subject to that Site’s own terms and policies. If you submit personal information to any of those Sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Site you visit. 

### Non-personally Identifiable Information

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personally identifiable information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about User’s means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

### WEB-BROWSER COOKIES 

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for the purpose of keeping records and tracking information about them. Users may choose to set their web-browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, Users need to remember that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

For detailed cookies policy please [click here](https://xnspy.com/cookie.html). 

### OTHER AGGREGATE INFORMATION 

If we gather demographic information from you (for example, your age, education level or household income), we will not share that information in a manner that identifies you as an individual with any other third party. Any information that might be shared with third parties will be aggregate information only ("aggregate" meaning demographic information speaking only to the broad characteristics of a group), unless we are required to release additional information under conditions described in next section "Legal Matters". 

### LEGAL MATTERS 

"XNSPY" considers your use of the service to be private. However, we may access or disclose information about you, your account, recorded information stored in your account and/or the content of your communications, in order to: (1) comply with the law or legal process served on us; (2) enforce and investigate potential violations of this contract; including use of this service to participate in, or facilitate, activities that violate the law; (3) investigate potential fraudulent activities; or (4) protect the rights, property, or safety of "XNSPY", its employees, its customers or the public. You consent to the access and disclosures outlined in this section. 

In the event of a change of control of XNSPY (such as through a merger, sale, assignment or liquidation of the business entity, or any of its properties, assets or equity) or, in the event of a direct or indirect sale of any of its publishing properties and/or its Site, personal information of users of the affected Sites in our possession will be transferred to the new owner/successor. We are not obligated to notify Site users of any such transaction. You may always change or delete your information or opt out by contacting us as provided below, or if the acquirer posts a new Privacy Policy with new contact information, you may change or delete your information or opt out by following any new instructions that are posted. 

###  HOW DO I OPT OUT OR CHANGE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?

To opt out of further e-mail communications from us, just click on the opt-out link or button in the e-mail, or contact us as instructed at the end of this Privacy Policy. We may need up to 30 days to assure compliance with your request.

To change your personal information that you have provided us, please contact us as instructed at the end of this Privacy Policy. 

### HOW WE USE THE COLLECTED INFORMATION

XNSPY may collect and use its Users’ personal information for the following purposes: 

  * To improve our Customer Support service
  * The information you provide helps us respond to your Customer Support requests and needs more efficiently.
  * To personalize user experience
  * We may use such information in the aggregate to understand how our Users, as a group, utilize the services and resources available on our Site.
  * To improve our Site
  * We may use your feedback to improve our products and services.
  * To process payments
  * We may use the information that our Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to deliver services provisioned by that order. We do not share this information with third parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other advertising event
  * We may send our Users the information they agreed to receive about the topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * To send periodic emails

We may use email addresses provided by our Users to send them the information and any updates on their order. Email addresses may also be used to respond to our Users’ inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If the User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, product or service-related information, etc. 

###  OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect your personal information, username, password, transaction information and other data stored on our Site against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction. 

Although we will exercise high levels of care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers and in storing that information on our systems, no method of transmission over the Internet, or of electronic storage, is 100% secure. As such, we cannot ensure or otherwise guarantee the security of information transmitted to us over the Internet. 

### CHANGES OR UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. We will post any changes to the Privacy Policy on the Site, but we have no other obligation to notify you of such changes. We indicate the date of the current version of this Privacy Policy below, so you know when it was last updated. Any changes will affect all of the information we have previously collected from you, as well as the information we collect after such changes, and may include without limitation additional uses or disclosures of your information. If any of the changes represent a material change that expands our use of personal information, the changes will be posted in advance of taking effect. We may post a prompt on the home page of our site for users to review the new Privacy Policy but are not required to do so. If you object to the changes, please contact us as provided below and we will remove your information that we previously collected. However, your subsequent provision of information to us through any of our Site is deemed your agreement to use of that information in accordance with the then-current Privacy Policy. 

### YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS 

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and Terms of Service. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of any changes to or modifications of this Privacy Policy will be deemed to constitute your full acceptance of those changes or modifications. 

### CONTACT US 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or you wish to make changes to your personal information or remove yourself from our database, please contact us in one of the following ways:

E-mail us at: [info@XNSPY.com ](mailto:info@XNSPY.com) and insert only the words "Re: Privacy Policy" in the subject line header of the e-mail. 

### DISCLAIMER 

You are advised that it is considered a violation of United States federal and/or state law in most instances to install surveillance software, such as the XNSPY Software, onto a mobile phone or other device for which you do not have proper authorization, and in most cases you are required to notify users of the device that they are being monitored. **It’s outright illegal to spy on your spouse, girlfriend/boyfriend, or partner using Xnspy.** Failure to do so is likely to result in violation of applicable law and may result in severe monetary and criminal penalties imposed on the violator. You should consult your own legal advisor with respect to legality of using the XNSPY Software in your jurisdiction prior to downloading and using the XNSPY Software.
